RHEA NAVARRO ESLER

Villa Zacate, Basak Pardo, Cebu City, Philippines 6000 Cell. No. 0932-1430207/0917-727-8662/(032)318-9457 Email Address: rhea_esler@yahoo.com

Career Objective

A challenging position in a Call Center industry

Summary

Experienced service assistant in a fast food industry in the Philippines with excellent customer service relations who can convince customers to become clients. With my skills in dealing with people through the company I worked with in abroad, it is a great factor in making customers feel important and significant since my determination to persuade customers is what I always look forward to.

Skills and Capabilities

- · Data entry with 50 wpm in typing
- Exceptional in written and oral communication
- Knowledgeable in MSWord and Excel
- Filing of documents
- Highly organized
- Business correspondence
- Client relations
- Good leadership skills

Work Experience

VCUSTOMER PHILIPPINES INCORPORATED

November 2012 - present

OPENLOOK BUSINESS SOLUTIONS

April 2012 - October 2012

October 2011-April 2012

SYKES ASIA INC.

- ✓ Provides customer service to clients and customers
- ✓ Resolves issues on their benefits and eligibility
- ✓ Provides assistance and sees to it that metrics performance are met so as to provide one-time resolution and customer satisfaction

STEAM GLOBAL SERVICES

June 2011 – September 2011

INTERCAT HOSPITALITY, LLC

Dubai Police Officers' Club, Dubai, UAE

Burger House, Dubai, UAE

Mashawi Lebanese Restaurant, Dubai, UAE

Cru Wine Bar, Dubai, UAE

- √ takes orders of Dubai Police Officers/customers
- √ acts as Cashier
- √ prepares Payroll

November, 2008 – August 2010

- ✓ makes order list of items, utensils and products needed
- ✓ makes inventory of sales and products
- √ prepares Sales Report
- √ takes care of Sales Invoices and makes data out of it

EMIRATES FLIGHT CATERING, LLC

August 2006 - October, 2008

- ✓ prepares food and equipment for the passengers of the aircraft
- √ makes inventory of items and materials
- √ takes care of customers' concerns and requests

FREEMONT FOOD CORP. (Jollibee)

December, 2004-April 2006

- √ acts as Service Crew
- √ maintaining 100% customer service satisfaction
- ✓ multi-tasking in all job specifications as cashier, cook and pantry

INA MICRO OPTO, CORP, MEPZ 2, Lapu-lapu City

January 2004 - July 2004

✓ acts as inspector for final packing of products

GREENWHICH PIZZA, CORP. (Ayala Center)

March 2003-September 2003

- √ acts as Service Crew
- √ doing standard operating procedures for making pizzas

Education

Elementary : University of San Jose-Recoletos - 1989 – 1995 Secondary : University of San Jose-Recoletos - 1995 – 1999

Tertiary : University of the Visayas (Undergrad)

Course: BSEd 2005

Character References

HON. ROBERTO A. CABARRUBIAS, City Councilor, Cebu City HON. YOLANDITO CAGANG, Brgy. Captain, Basak Pardo, Cebu City HON. XERCES NAVARRO, Brgy. Treasurer, Basak Pardo, Cebu City